Review Exercise 156, Reading Reduced Sounds. Think the United Auto Workers can
beat Caterpillar Incorporated in their bitter contract battle?
Before placing your beds, talk to Paul Brannon, who can't wait to cross the
picket line at Caterpillar's factory in East Peoria. Brannon recently laid off by
a rubber parts plant where he earned base pay of six dollars and thirty cents an
hour lives one block from a heavily picketed gate at the cat complex now he's
applying to replace one of 12,600 workers
who have been on strike for the past five months seventeen dollars an hour and they
don't want to work asked Brannon I don't want to take another guy's job but I'm
hurting too.